SolarWinds Server & Application Monitor (SAM) AppInsight Automation scripts
========================================================

To learn about PowerShell scripts included in this folder, see the following Success Center link:
https://documentation.solarwinds.com/en/Success_Center/SAM/Content/SAM-AppInsight-Automate-Configuration.htm

Notices
============

--Depending on how it's configured, PowerShell can make your deployment vulnerable
to unauthorized access. Your organization should internally review and assess to 
what extent PowerShell scripts are incorporated into your environment. For details,
see https://documentation.solarwinds.com/en/Success_Center/SAM/Content/SAM-PowerShell-sw3460.htm

--The scripts are not supported under any SolarWinds support program or service. 
--The scripts are provided AS IS without warranty of any kind. SolarWinds further 
--disclaims all warranties including, without limitation, any implied warranties
--of merchantability or of fitness for a particular purpose. The risk arising 
--out of the use or performance of the scripts and documentation stays with you. 
--In no event shall SolarWinds or anyone else involved in the creation, production, 
--or delivery of the scripts be liable for any damages whatsoever (including, 
--without limitation, damages for loss of business profits, business interruption, 
--loss of business information, or other pecuniary loss) arising out of the use 
--of or inability to use the scripts or documentation.
